## Abdush Shomad Bukhori

xom.albukhori@gmail.com | 6285731229262

I am an IT professional with 4 years of experience in developing web or mobile based applications. Think critically in solving problems effectively and efficiently. Have good communication skills and love to discuss about the issues in application development.

The scope of applications that I have developed include Hospitality, Healthcare, E-Commerce, Onlineshop, Company Profile, Games, E-Vote, Personal Blog and Fintech.

The Featured Technology Stack that I use include Codeigniter Framework, Golang, ReactJS, Flutter, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Firebase.

## Experience

#### **Acting Head of IT Department**

Jun 2021 - Sep 2022

Mamalyfe (PT. Mamalyfe Selalu Diberkati), Surabaya, East Java (Indonesia)

- Provide consultation and strategic advice to achieve business objectives
- Collaborate with the Sales Marketing team to help with the sales process
- Communicate professionally with vendors, IT team, Customer Service team, designer team, content creator team, and management
- Troubleshoot issues that come out in applications both backend, frontend, database and server
- Analyze business requirements and provide estimates of work required
- Create Concepts/Ideas to be implemented in Applications
- Scheduling work time related to application features that are developed
- Designing Database & Workflow related to developed features
- Guiding the team in developing features according to the design that has been made
- Coding and Testing both Backend (API, Third party Integration) and Frontend (Assist Team when needed)

IT Project Manager Mar 2019 - Apr 2021

Alfath Tech (PT. Alfath Teknologi Kreatif), Malang, East Java (Indonesia)

- Create Application required by company and client
- Maintaining the Application that has been created in accordance with the cooperation agreement with the client
- Provide consultation and strategic advice to achieve application development goals by company and client
- Communicate professionally with IT team, Customer Service team, and management
- Troubleshoot issues that come out in the company's own app
- Analyze business requirements and provide estimates of work required
- Create Concepts/Ideas to be implemented in Applications
- Scheduling work time related to application features that are developed
- Designing Workflow related to developed features
- Guiding the team in developing features according to the design that has been made
- Coding and Testing both Backend and Frontend

IT Manager Aug 2018 - Apr 2021

Kelola.net, Malang, East Java (Indonesia)

- Create Web Application required by the company
- Maintaining the Web Application that has been created
- Provide consultation and strategic advice to achieve business objectives
- Collaborate with the Sales Marketing team to help with the sales process
- Communicate professionally with IT team, Customer Service team, designer team, content creator team, and management
- Troubleshoot issues that come out in applications both backend, frontend, database and server
- Analyze business requirements and provide estimates of work required
- Create Concepts/Ideas to be implemented in Applications
- Scheduling work time related to application features that are developed
- Designing Database & Workflow related to developed features
- Coding and Testing both Backend and Frontend
- Do Online and Offline Training Sessions regarding the Use of Applications for users

Software Developer Oct 2017 - Jul 2018

Syariahrooms Hospitality (CV. Alfath Berkah Mandiri), Malang, East Java (Indonesia)

- Create information systems required by the company
- Maintaining the Information System that has been created
- Create features required by the company

# Skills & Specialization

Project Estimation, Project Coordination, Project Management, Project Planning, Cross-functional Team Leadership, Web Development, Android Development, Programming, Back-End Web Development, PHP Applications, Go (Programming Language), Web Services API, API Development, Web Services, Front-End Development, Software Development, Model-View-Controller (MVC), Application Programming Interfaces, Express. js, Kotlin, Laravel, Firebase, Codelgniter, Android, Bootstrap, PHP, PhpMyAdmin, AJAX, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), HTML, jQuery, HTML5, PostgreSQL, MySQL, React.js, Flutter, JavaScript, GitHub, Git, SQL, Node.js, Team Leadership, Teamwork

### Education

### Universitas Islam Negeri Maulana Malik Ibrahim Malang

Jul 2015 - Nov 2021

Bachelor's Degree, Informatics Engineering Malang, East Java (Indonesia)

Bachelor of Computer Science - Grade: 3.58

- Member of the Informatics Engineering Student Association for the period 2018-2019
- Website Developer Mentor Coordinator at the 2018 Summer Program held by the Department of Informatics
- Laboratory Assistant Department of Informatics Engineering 2016-2017 and 2017-2018

1/1/	$\sim$	1+00
V/ V/	1	ites
vv	-	

https://asbukhori.github.io